<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Vokke']]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Vokke']]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/vokke/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 23:49:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/vokke/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The feeling of home]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The feeling of home</h1><p>To this day there is no where i have been that calls to me like my famlies homestead farm in the north Georgia mountains.  It is a place that my whole childhood urned for.  It was a place of adventure, mystery, beauty and amazement.   My ancestors were homestead mountain people who lived of the land and with it.  Our heritage is rooted in growing and providing for ourselves.  My granny and pawpaw were big flower enthusiasts and could name the hundreds and hundreds of species and subspecies of flower on our farm.  This still amazes me today.  This is special image to me as it will always remind me of the walk up to the old house.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d3c8a26323e300c9f0a92107325230ad737fbbca.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vokke/3e5adb78-2dfb-46a0-928c-aa4e71a18667/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3e5adb78-2dfb-46a0-928c-aa4e71a18667</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 23:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The morning light of fog and pines]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The morning light of fog and pines</h1><p>On a cold and humid morning in the pine forests outside Bainbridge Ga. I walked out into this inspiring moment.  Taken on the start of  long day of working on the plantation.  I had just pulled up to the office when out back i looked upon a moment i had to stop and take in.  I grabbed my Canon and watched as the warm golden sun cut through the rising fog as if a blade through water.   Needless to say those days in that amazing place filled my soul with memories i will never forget.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/dd21b61cb4a70b1da08d762cd4e93be33d49bed1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vokke/c1b536a7-9f0d-4242-a262-6187c44f7b8d/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b536a7-9f0d-4242-a262-6187c44f7b8d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 23:22:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A long Journey]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A long Journey</h1><p>The long trek up Mt. Washington in New Hampshire was worth the 7 hours of climbing and hiking when I came upon this breathtaking view.  As the clouds filled the cold sky i sat and listened to the sound of the earth singing.   The sound of wind, water, and earth all in sync.  the colors of fall filling the forest and painting a masterpiece of amazement.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8650ce0920e6b7f1cc7bd9053cda043c1e6e458c.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vokke/70c1b3b5-136f-41f7-ad99-bddbaa44ed56/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">70c1b3b5-136f-41f7-ad99-bddbaa44ed56</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 23:22:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An enlightened moment]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An enlightened moment</h1><p>It was roughly 8 years ago as i walked out onto the beach on the Pacific northwest coast of Washington state.   I had to trek 2 miles through the tall magnificent forests of the Olympic Mountains.  As i stepped foot onto the beach i was in awe.  Mainly of the extreme tide drop...  litterally 10-15 feet.  It was like nothing i had ever seen.  Mountains rising out of the ocean, created by 1000's of years of erosion.  Starfish every were, a species i had yet to see.  The experience i feel is summed up in this capture that to this day truly speaks to me.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6eb03306e715f57c0450179d906d8192e6d99eb3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vokke/f567eee7-e7c6-480d-b78e-e616df6aea52/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f567eee7-e7c6-480d-b78e-e616df6aea52</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 23:23:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Downtown Adventures]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Downtown Adventures</h1><p>Most people likely wouldn't think of a city as an outdoor landscape.  Yet i found out living in downtown Tampa Fl. a few years ago that they are indeed an ecosystem of their own.  I walked past this view as so many other in the bay side city.  As i was roaming the streets with my camera one summer evening i found a city empty and inviting. The sound was still and erie as the traffic lights blinked in their endless cycle as if there were cars waiting for that signal of progression.  I walked towards the sound of music in curiosity as to where it might be coming from.  To my surprise i stumbled onto the oldest bar in town playing jams on the jukebox which could be heard throughout the streets.  It was at this moment that i knew that the night was delivering me to unique moment that i had to capture.  with ony minimal editing the lights did amazing things in the heavy and humid air.  With a 6 minute exposure i achieved the reflection of the moment.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/556b4695ef4dc544861bf58fc2434ba51ca3097d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vokke/5914db7a-4216-449b-aa77-0dd68263480b/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5914db7a-4216-449b-aa77-0dd68263480b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 23:22:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>